So hello everyone, this is the
share of TV18 Broadcast. Next, let us
look at the quarterly results of the share. So, here the
total income of the share was
28352 on a quarterly basis and this number is
in lakhs and now here the
income on a quarterly basis has become 35000 to 11
lakhs here. Next, let us
talk about the total expenses of the share, so here it is
29000.15. The expenses on a yearly basis have
increased to
3742 lakhs here. Next, let us
look at the total comprehensive income of the share,
so the
income on a quarterly basis was 50062 lakhs which increased to one thousand 425. Let us
talk about the earnings per share, so here the
earning per share was 3 paise.
Now the quarterly increase in this has become
12 paise, that is, overall the
results of this share have been good here.
If you have this stock and you
want to hold it here with a long term perspective, then
you can hold it here
and tomorrow you will
also get to see immense circuit momentum in this stock.